Darshan Arun Jadhav Bengaluru, Karnataka | Phone: 9380725710 
Email: jadhavdarshan006@gmail.com                     LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/darshan-jadhav-915b10372/ 
PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY: A Computer Science Engineering graduate (2025) with 1 Year of hands-on 
experience in Wordpress and 6 Months of experience in Frontend development. Proficient in HTML, CSS, 
JavaScript, SQL, & GitHub with a strong foundation in software development principles and data structures. 
EDUCATION: 
Bachelor of Engineering (B.E.) In Computer Science 
Maratha Mandal Engineering College - Belagavi Karnataka – 591113. 
CGPA: 7.98/10.0 | Graduation Year: June 2025. 
Diploma In Computer Science 
Jain Polytechnic Belagavi Karnataka – 590014. 
Percentage: 67% | Graduation Year: October 2022. 
SKILLS: 
• Technical skills: Wordpress, Figma, SQL, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3, React. 
• Developer Tools: Git, GitHub, Visual Studio 
 
WORK EXPERIENCE: 
Master Web Works (Wordpress Developer) as Freelancer (Jan 2025 – Present) 
• Engaged in comprehensive training on Wordpress development standards and best practices for 
enterprise- level Websites. 
• Assisted in Designing and Creating New Webpages and Collaborated with senior engineer to 
understand How Themes and Plugins Works on Webpages while creating Websites. 
 
INTERNSHIP EXPERIENCE: 
 AI-DevOps Engineer| Rooman Technologies Pvt Ltd in Association With IBM. (Sep 2024 - May 2025) 
Rooman Technologies offers AI-assisted DevOps training that teaches how to use local large language models 
(LLMs) to enhance productivity, automate shell script and Docker file generation, secure compliance, and optimize 
costs. 
Frontend Developer Intern| JSpiders Training Institute (Mar 2025 – Dec 2025) 
JSpiders offer Frontend Development training teaches that how to enhance Web Technologies, GitHub Files and SQL 
got hands on experience with live projects and with presentation skills. 
 
PROJECTS: 
• Car Driving School Management System (HTML/CSS, JS, MY SQL) 
o A DBMS project facilitating student registration, course scheduling, and administrative 
functions efficiently. 
o Managed where the student should leave the Car after Training also in which KM 
should be mentioned while using. 
• Hand Simulation (python, open CV) 
o The project uses Pygame and OpenCV to create dynamic picture animations and 
computer graphics, enhancing digital content with advanced technology. 
• Bus Reservation system (HTML/CSS, JS, Django) 
o The project builds a RedBus clone with Django, featuring Booking, user authentication, 
recommendations in a scalable Services.  
o The Platform was created to aid students in understanding fundamental physics concepts 
through dynamic, hands-on visualization. 
• Attendances With Face  
o The project develops a fitness tracker for well-being, monitoring physical activity to 
promote a healthier lifestyle through insightful analytics.  
  Languages: 
 English, Hindi, Kannada, Marathi